{
    "results":[
        {
            "question": "Seinfeld is often described as a show about",
            "correct_answer": "Nothing",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Psychopaths",
                "New York",
                "Philosophy"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is Jerry's nemesis?",
            "correct_answer": "Newman",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Negan",
                "Lippman",
                "Dugan"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What restaurant do Jerry and friends frequently visit?",
            "correct_answer": "Monk's Cafe",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Canter's Deli",
                "Katz's Deli",
                "Dom's Cafe"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What does George want to name his firstborn child?",
            "correct_answer": "Seven",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Blue",
                "Yankee",
                "Six"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "In \"The Pony Remark\" where was Manya an immigrant from?",
            "correct_answer": "Poland",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Germany",
                "Italy",
                "Ireland"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "In \"The Heart Attack\", Elaine interprets Jerry's scrawled note as what?",
            "correct_answer": "Don't mess with Johnny",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Fix me some Halibut",
                "Salami Salami Turkey",
                "Flaming globes of Sigmond"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "In \"The Robbery\", what is the one flaw in Jerry's door's lock?",
            "correct_answer": "The door must be closed",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "The lock must be turned in a certain way",
                "The door needs to be closed gently",
                "The lock doesn't work"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "In \"The Cafe\", what is the first score Elaine gets on the I.Q. test?",
            "correct_answer": "85",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "95",
                "100",
                "151"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of George's convict girlfriend?",
            "correct_answer": "Celia",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Tara",
                "Susan",
                "Audrey"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Who leaves a smell in Jerry's car?",
            "correct_answer": "Valet",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Puddy",
                "Newman",
                "Kramer"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which company is Kramer striking against in episode 166?",
            "correct_answer": "H and H Bagels",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Kenny Rogers Roasters",
                "Bagel Hut",
                "Central Perk"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What famous actress plays Jerry's wife in order to get a discount on dry cleaning?",
            "correct_answer": "Courtney Cox",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Lori Loughlin",
                "Kathy Griffin",
                "Teri Hatcher"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What caused major problems on Kramer's stretch of adopted highway?",
            "correct_answer": "Kramer painted over the lines to widen the lanes",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Kramer parked on the median strip",
                "Kramer left the litter on the median strip",
                "Kramer never took care of it"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Jerry Seinfeld's birthday?",
            "correct_answer": "April 29, 1954",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "May 28, 1953",
                "April 29, 1953",
                "March 28, 1954"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Noreen's \"high-talker\" boyfriend?",
            "correct_answer": "Dan",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Joe",
                "Drake",
                "Dave"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Jerry described one of Elaine's boyfriends as \"a male bimbo, he's a mimbo\". What was his name?",
            "correct_answer": "Tony",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Puddy",
                "Tim",
                "Todd"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the name of the \"low-talker\" who designed the puffy shirt that Jerry unknowingly agreed to wear on the Today Show?",
            "correct_answer": "Leslie",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Lisi",
                "Lily",
                "Lanette"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "In the first episode, what kind of greeting does Jerry get from the girl he was meeting at the airport?",
            "correct_answer": "The surprise blindfold greeting",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "A hug",
                "The handshake sandwich greeting",
                "A kiss on the cheek"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Who said \"Climbers keepers\"?",
            "correct_answer": "Newman",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Frank Costanza",
                "Puddy",
                "George Steinbrenner"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What kind of pasta was Kramer going to make a George figurine out of?",
            "correct_answer": "Ravioli",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Rigatoni",
                "Elbow",
                "Penne"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the name of the bad tennis player who sold Jerry a racket?",
            "correct_answer": "Milos",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Miguel",
                "Fernando",
                "Dmitri"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What was the name of the video store guy that Elaine liked?",
            "correct_answer": "Vincent",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Vito",
                "David",
                "Gene"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "Jerry's parents live in what retirement complex?",
            "correct_answer": "Del Boca Vista",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Retirement Village of Pensacola",
                "Del Vista Boca",
                "Pensacola Retirement Village"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What hat does Elaine choose to put on the cover of the J Peterman catalog?",
            "correct_answer": "The Urban Sombrero",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Santa Fe Cardigan",
                "Hamptons Classic Shawl",
                "Casual Low Pump Sandal"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What brand of golf ball does George pull out of the whale's blow hole?",
            "correct_answer": "Titleist",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Srixon",
                "Nike",
                "Callaway"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "What are the names of the hostile male couple that confront Kramer in \"The Soup Nazi\"?",
            "correct_answer": "Bob and Ray",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Bob and Cedric",
                "Bill and Ray",
                "Bill and Cedric"
            ]
        }
    ]
}